## HR SERVICE CONTACT CENTER REPRESENTATIVE

Summary

Over 10 years of providing excellent customer service and supervisory skills. Outstanding ability to perform effectively in an unpredictable, fast-paced environment. Strong verbal and written communication skills coupled with the ability to utilize my critical thinking attributes to originate, create, and resolve problems. Driven to achieve company goals to become the best asset to my organization Highlights

- HRST, QueWeb, Knowledge Base
- People Soft, Manager Self-Service
- Kronos, AIMS, LOA Database, Employee Self Service
- Microsoft Office: Work, Power Point, Excel, Access, Outlook, Publisher

## Experience

December 2015 to Current

Camino Nuevo Charter Academy Los Angeles, CA HR Service Contact Center Representative

- Responsible for processing staffing needs, HR transactions, Wage garnishments, Leave of absence, Manual checks, Benefits administration,
  Time and attendance, Batching hours, Ad-hoc reports, and providing excellent customer service to over 2248 locations in the US, Puerto
  Rico, and Virgin Islands.
- Support over 450,000 current and former associates (domestic and international) with payroll/HR related inquires.
- Process multiple forms for various employee changes, hires and terminations.
- Team Lead to new training classes to teach and develop new associates.Â
- Partner with supervisors to plan events to improve associate engagement by creating action plans, training material and recognition programs
  to create efficiency throughout the call team.
- Collaborate with the field to assist with pre/post employment processes, scheduling, performance management, and HR Policy and Procedures.
- Partner with retail staffing to manage the full life cycle of recruiting components including, research, posting jobs, sourcing with traditional
  and social media networks, interviewing, and processing background checks.Â
- Responsible for collaborating with AACG to facilitate communication channels with supervisors, employees and between the two, ensuring
  that proper HR policies and procedures are communicated and followed, while maintaining compliance with federal and state regulations. Â

December 2014 to January 2016

Medstar Health Saint Mary's, MD Property Manager

Managing Properties, Answering Phones, Making Collection Calls, Tendering Payments, Leasing Storage Units, Conducting Auctions.

December 2013 to December 2014

Progressive Novato, CA Business Office Associate

- Preparing Bank Deposits, Answering Multi-line Phones Title and Tag Processing, Processing DMV Paperwork, Processing Contracts for Lien Holders, Tendering All Payments.
- Conducted new employee orientationÂ
- Prepared and sent on boarding welcome packages to new employees.Â

March 2008 to December 2010

Faurecia Interior Systems Leipzig, DE Customer Service Representative

• Store Inventory Stock/ Audit, Commercial Shipping and Billing, Tendering Sales, Processing Card Applications.

February 2006 to August 2011

Lutheran Services In Iowa Wapello, IA Supervisor

- Supervised 60 people at various locations, Communicated with the guests by delivering outstanding guest service, Handled all guest compliments and concerns,.
- Scheduled 60 employees weekly for various locations, January 2006 to Six Flags Over Ga.
- Assisted with the preparation of the performance review process.Â
- Performed and administers special projects as needed.Â

February 2006 to August 2011

Six Flags Over GA City, STATE Administrative Assistant

Answered phone calls, Tracked and recorded park attendance every hour into the park and corporate database for both Six Flags White
Water and Six Flags over Georgia, Data Entry Served as the "point of contact" for all problems/ issues that may have occurred during daily
park operation.

Education

Art Institute of Atlanta

City, State Interior Design Bachelor of Arts Interior Design

Interest

Atlanta Metropolitan State College: Head Cheer: Coach Lithia Christian Academy: Assistant Cheer Coach Georgia High School Association: Cheer Judge

- Partner with internal and external vendors to determine necessary requirements and ensure that needs a met in a timely manner.Â
- Assist budget committee with managing monthly P&L and invoice processing to ensure timely payments.Â

## Skills

Ad-Hoc Reports, AIMS, Attention to detail, Benefits administration, Billing, Interpersonal skills, Contracts, Excellent customer service, Data Entry, Database, Human Resource, HR, Inventory, Kronos, Leadership, Managing, Access, Excel, Microsoft Office, Outlook, Power Point, Publisher, Organization skills, Payroll, Payroll Processing, People Soft, Sales, Shipping, Staffing, Supervisory.

Additional Information

• Interests Atlanta Metropolitan State College: Head Cheer Coach Lithia Christian Academy: Assistant Cheer Coach Georgia High School Association: Cheer Judge